<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' ?>
<Trials_downloaded_from_ICTRP>

    
  <Trial><Export_date>02/03/2024 14:32:58</Export_date>
    <Internal_Number>13140733
    </Internal_Number>
    <TrialID>IRCT20090301001722N29
    </TrialID>
    <Last_Refreshed_on>26 June 2023
    </Last_Refreshed_on>
    <Public_title>Effects of Electrical stimulation and Whole Body vibration therapy with transcranial direct current stimulation on spactic cerebral palsy children
    </Public_title>
    <Scientific_title>Comparison of the conjunct effects of Electrical Stimulation and Whole-Body Vibration Therapy with Transcranial Direct Current Stimulation and Whole-body Vibration Therapy on Balance and Function in Spastic Cerebral Palsy Children.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                         
    </Scientific_title>
    <Primary_sponsor>Tehran University of Medical Sciences
    </Primary_sponsor>
    <Retrospective_flag>No
    </Retrospective_flag>
    <Date_registration3>20230615
    </Date_registration3>
    <Date_registration>2023-06-15
    </Date_registration>
    <Source_Register>IRCT
    </Source_Register>
    <web_address>http://en.irct.ir/trial/70443
    </web_address>
    <Recruitment_Status>Recruiting
    </Recruitment_Status>
    <other_records>No
    </other_records>
    <Inclusion_agemin>5 years
    </Inclusion_agemin>
    <Inclusion_agemax>15 years
    </Inclusion_agemax>
    <Inclusion_gender>Both
    </Inclusion_gender>
    <Date_enrollement>2023-06-05
    </Date_enrollement>
    <Target_size>42
    </Target_size>
    <Study_type>interventional
    </Study_type>
    <Study_design>Randomization: Randomized, Blinding: Double blinded, Placebo: Not used, Assignment: Parallel, Purpose: Treatment, Randomization description: Before the process of randomization, we will screen all the participants and assign them a unique number from 1 to 42. Then the process of randomization will be carried out using Random Allocation software version 1.0 (developed by the Department of Anaesthesia, Isfahan University of Medical Sciences, Isfahan, Iran). It is a randomization software for parallel group trials. It requires the total sample size and the total number of groups. We will add a total sample size of 42 participants and 3 groups into the software with only one block. The software generates an output file that can be opened with internet explorer. The output file contains a list of number along with assigned groups. In our case, the groups will be A, B, C with 14 participants in each group. Then this sequence will be used for participant allocation in the study grou
    </Study_design>
    <Phase>N/A
    </Phase>
    <Countries>Pakistan
    </Countries>
    <Contact_Firstname>Dr.Mohammad-Reza Hadian Rasanani
    </Contact_Firstname>
    <Contact_Lastname/>
    <Contact_Address>Rehabilitation Faculty, Pich e Shemiran, Enghelab Street Tehran Tehran Iran,
    </Contact_Address>
    <Contact_Email>hadianrasan@gmail.com
    </Contact_Email>
    <Contact_Tel>+98 21 8891 3469
    </Contact_Tel>
    <Contact_Affiliation>Tehran University of Medical Sciences
    </Contact_Affiliation>
    <Inclusion_Criteria>Inclusion criteria: Age of 5- 15 years.&lt;br&gt;Both Genders (Boys and Girls).&lt;br&gt;Children diagnosed with Spastic Hemiplegic cerebral palsy.&lt;br&gt;Degree of Spasticity Grade 1, 1+, and 2 according to Modified Ashworth Scale in the following muscles (hip flexors, hip adductors, hamstrings and ankle plantar flexors).&lt;br&gt;Level I(Can walk indoors and outdoors and climb stairs without using hands for support, and II (ability to walk indoors and outdoors and climb stairs with a railing ) of Gross Motor Function Classification System.&lt;br&gt;Manual Ability Classification System level I to IV.&lt;br&gt;No history of epilepsy.&lt;br&gt;No unhealed fractures.&lt;br&gt;No visual impairments and auditory impairments.&lt;br&gt;Not taking botulinum toxin injections.&lt;br&gt;Does not have any sensory and motor loss.&lt;br&gt;Does not have cardiopulmonary problems.&lt;br&gt;Does not have recent surgery (less than 1 year).&lt;br&gt;Children who would not experience joint contractures&lt;br&gt;Children with no Muscle or tendon inflammation&lt;br&gt;Children with no Leg length discrepancy
    </Inclusion_Criteria>
    <Exclusion_Criteria>Exclusion criteria: The child or the guardian is not interested to carry out the study.&lt;br&gt;Failing to complete the study.
    </Exclusion_Criteria>
    <Condition>Cerbral Palsy. &lt;br&gt;G80;Cerebral P
    </Condition>
    <Intervention>Intervention 1: Intervention group 1 WBV training for 20 min a day,4 days a week for 4 weeks. The children will be instructed to maintain a standing posture on the vibration platform. Children will stand barefooted with feet parallel and in slight flexion (30°). The feet will be placed at an equal distance from the center line of the device when standing. During the 20 min of therapy, every 3 minutes of vibration training and 2 minutes of rest will be repeated 4 times. The frequency of the WBV stimulation will be (12–18 Hz) and will achieve gradually increase by 1 Hz per 2 seconds, till the desired frequency is achieved. Intervention 2: Intervention group 2 WBV training for 20 min a day,4 days a week for 4 weeks. The children will be instructed to maintain a standing posture on the vibration platform. Children will stand barefooted with feet parallel and in slight flexion (30°). The feet will be placed at an equal distance from the center line of the device when standing. During the 20 min of therapy, every 3 minutes of vibration training and 2 minutes of rest will be repeated 4 times. The frequency of the WBV stimulation will be (12–18 Hz) and will achieve gradually increase by 1 Hz per 2 seconds, till the desired frequency is achieved. Functional Electrical stimulation with Rectangular biphasic pulses with a pulse width of 250 µs, the stimulus intensity 70 mA, and a frequency ranged from 40 Hz,4 days a week for 4 weeks will be administered on motor points of the spastic muscles mainly for the lower extremity ( quadriceps and gastrocnemius and soleus). Intervention 3: Intervention group 3 Transcranial Direct Current Stimulation (tDCS) will be given with 2mA intensity for 20 min a day,4 days sessions a week for 4 weeks. 5*7 cm square electrodes will be placed as Anodal 
    </Intervention>
    <Primary_outcome>Range of Motion. Timepoint: Before and After the intervention for Upper  and lower extremity joints. Method of measurement: Universal Goniometer.;Hand Grip Strength. Timepoint: Before and After the intervention for Upper Limb. Method of measurement: Hand Held Digital Dynamometer.;Isometric Muscle strength test. Timepoint: Before and After the intervention for  lower extremity muscles. Method of measurement: digital force gauge SF-500.;Centre of Gravity, and Balance test scores. Timepoint: Before and After the intervention for  lower extremity. Method of measurement: Nintendo Wii-Fit, Balance board.;Gait parameters (walking speed, cadence(stride length and step length) using cinematography. Timepoint: Before and after the intervention for the lower extremity. Method of measurement: Kinovea software version 0.9.5.;Timed up and go test. Timepoint: Before and After the intervention. Method of measurement: One Chair, Measurement Tape and Stop Watch.;Manual dexterity. Timepoint: before and after the intervention for the upper extremity. Method of measurement: 9 hole and peg board.;Modified Ashworth Scale. Timepoint: before and after intervention for upper and lower extremity. Method of measurement: Modified Ashworth Scale Questionnaire.;Berg balance scale. Timepoint: before and after the intervention for spastic Cerebral palsy children. Method of measurement: Berg Balance scale questioner.;Gross motor function. Timepoint: before and after the intervention for spastic crebral palsy children. Method of measurement: GMFM-88 scale ( Standing and sitting component).
    </Primary_outcome>
    <Source_Support>Tehran University of Medical Sciences
    </Source_Support>
    <Ethics_review_status>Approved
    </Ethics_review_status>
    <Ethics_review_approval_date>31/05/2023
    </Ethics_review_approval_date>
    <Ethics_review_contact_name/>
    <Ethics_review_contact_address>Tehran University of Medical Sciences (TUMS)
    </Ethics_review_contact_address>
    <Ethics_review_contact_phone/>
    <Ethics_review_contact_email/>
    <results_url_link/>
    
  </Trial>

    
  <Trial><Export_date>02/03/2024 14:32:58</Export_date>
    <Internal_Number>12510684
    </Internal_Number>
    <TrialID>IRCT20220725055552N1
    </TrialID>
    <Last_Refreshed_on>29 August 2022
    </Last_Refreshed_on>
    <Public_title>The effect of electrical stimulation in the treatment of upper limbs of cerebral palsy
    </Public_title>
    <Scientific_title>The effect of Transcranial Directed Current Stimulation on upper limb function in children with unilateral cerebral palsy                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                       
    </Scientific_title>
    <Primary_sponsor>Shahid Beheshti University of Medical Sciences
    </Primary_sponsor>
    <Retrospective_flag>No
    </Retrospective_flag>
    <Date_registration3>20220727
    </Date_registration3>
    <Date_registration>2022-07-27
    </Date_registration>
    <Source_Register>IRCT
    </Source_Register>
    <web_address>http://en.irct.ir/trial/64932
    </web_address>
    <Recruitment_Status>Not Recruiting
    </Recruitment_Status>
    <other_records>No
    </other_records>
    <Inclusion_agemin>5 years
    </Inclusion_agemin>
    <Inclusion_agemax>10 years
    </Inclusion_agemax>
    <Inclusion_gender>Both
    </Inclusion_gender>
    <Date_enrollement>2022-07-26
    </Date_enrollement>
    <Target_size>50
    </Target_size>
    <Study_type>interventional
    </Study_type>
    <Study_design>Randomization: Randomized, Blinding: Double bli
    </Study_design>
    <Phase>3
    </Phase>
    <Countries>Iran (Islamic Republic of);Iran (Islamic Republic of)
    </Countries>
    <Contact_Firstname>Behnam Ghaderian
    </Contact_Firstname>
    <Contact_Lastname/>
    <Contact_Address>Seventh Floor, Haft Tir Crossroad, the beginning of Student Blvd., in front of the police station clinic, Ghasemi Alley, Arad Doctors Building, 7th floor
    </Contact_Address>
    <Contact_Email>behnamgh7491@gmail.com
    </Contact_Email>
    <Contact_Tel>+98 26 3271 5709
    </Contact_Tel>
    <Contact_Affiliation>Shahid Beheshti University of Medical Sciences
    </Contact_Affiliation>
    <Inclusion_Criteria>Inclusion criteria: The person must be a hemiplegic cerebral palsy&lt;br&gt;The person must be 5-10 years old&lt;br&gt;The person without unstable medical conditions such as seizures
    </Inclusion_Criteria>
    <Exclusion_Criteria>Exclusion criteria: Failure to attend more than one meeting.&lt;br&gt;Non-cooperation of children and their families until the end of the regular study period
    </Exclusion_Criteria>
    <Condition>Hemiplegia  cerebral palsy. &lt;br&gt;Spastic hemiplegic cerebral palsy;G80.2
    </Condition>
    <Intervention>Intervention 1: his group performed routine occupational therapy exercises for 45 minutes along with transcranial direct electrical stimulation technique, in which a low direct electric current with an intensity of 1.5-2 mV is injected into the primary motor area of the healthy hemisphere with a tDCS device. They receive for twenty minutes in each session and for twenty sessions in a period of one month. Intervention 2: Control group: This group receives routine occupational therapy exercises for forty-five minutes in each session and twenty sessions in a one-month period, and also to blind the participant, an electrical stimulation device is placed on the primary motor area of the healthy hemisphere for twenty minutes in each session. It can be done, but the stimulation does not take place.
    </Intervention>
    <Primary_outcome>Motor function of the upper limb. Timepoint: At the beginning of the intervention and after the end of the intervention. Method of measurement: Fugl-Meyer test.
    </Primary_outcome>
    <Secondary_outcome>Upper limb coordination. Timepoint: The beginning and end of the intervention. Method of measurement: Bruininks-Oseretsky test.;Upper limb Integration. Timepoint: The beginning and end of the intervention. Method of measurement: Bruininks-Oseretsky test.;Precision of fine movement. Timepoint: The beginning and end of the intervention. Method of measurement: Bruininks-Oseretsky test.;Upper extremity speed. Timepoint: The beginning and end of the intervention. Method of measurement: Box and block test.;Dexterity of Upper extremity. Timepoint: The beginning and end of the intervention. Method of measurement: Bruininks-Oseretsky test.
    </Secondary_outcome>
    <Source_Support>no
    </Source_Support>
    <Ethics_review_status>Approved
    </Ethics_review_status>
    <Ethics_review_approval_date>15/05/2022
    </Ethics_review_approval_date>
    <Ethics_review_contact_name/>
    <Ethics_review_contact_address>Ethics Committee of Shahid Beheshti University of Medical Sciences
    </Ethics_review_contact_address>
    <Ethics_review_contact_phone/>
    <Ethics_review_contact_email/>
    <results_url_link/>
    
  </Trial>

    
  <Trial><Export_date>02/03/2024 14:32:58</Export_date>
    <Internal_Number>10897852
    </Internal_Number>
    <TrialID>ChiCTR2100042452
    </TrialID>
    <Last_Refreshed_on>26 April 2021
    </Last_Refreshed_on>
    <Public_title>Improvement of central cortical functional re-organization and compensation after ectopic neurorrhaphy for peripheral nerve injury using repetitive transcranial magnetic stimulation combined with biofeedback peripheral electrical stimulation
    </Public_title>
    <Scientific_title>Improvement of central cortical functional re-organization and compensation after ectopic neurorrhaphy for peripheral nerve injury using repetitive transcranial magnetic stimulation combined with biofeedback peripheral electrical stimulation                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                               
    </Scientific_title>
    <Primary_sponsor>Beijing Neurosurgical Institute
    </Primary_sponsor>
    <Retrospective_flag>Yes
    </Retrospective_flag>
    <Date_registration3>20210121
    </Date_registration3>
    <Date_registration>2021-01-21
    </Date_registration>
    <Source_Register>ChiCTR
    </Source_Register>
    <web_address>http://www.chictr.org.cn/showproj.aspx?proj=65511
    </web_address>
    <Recruitment_Status>Recruiting
    </Recruitment_Status>
    <other_records>No
    </other_records>
    <Inclusion_agemin>18
    </Inclusion_agemin>
    <Inclusion_agemax>65
    </Inclusion_agemax>
    <Inclusion_gender>Both
    </Inclusion_gender>
    <Date_enrollement>2021-03-01
    </Date_enrollement>
    <Target_size>1:50;2:50;3:50;
    </Target_size>
    <Study_type>Interventional study
    </Study_type>
    <Study_design>Parallel
    </Study_design>
    <Phase>0
    </Phase>
    <Countries>china
    </Countries>
    <Contact_Firstname>Liu Song
    </Contact_Firstname>
    <Contact_Lastname/>
    <Contact_Address>119 South Fourth Ring Road West, Fengtai District, Beijing 
    </Contact_Address>
    <Contact_Email>dr_songliu2018@163.com
    </Contact_Email>
    <Contact_Tel>+86 10-59975050
    </Contact_Tel>
    <Contact_Affiliation>Beijing Neurosurgical Institute
    </Contact_Affiliation>
    <Inclusion_Criteria>Inclusion criteria: 1. Aged 18-65 years;&#x0D;&lt;br&gt;2. have facial nerve palsy symptoms between 0-24 months, the palsy could be triggered by all kinds of reason;&#x0D;&lt;br&gt;3. both sides of the Hypoglossal nerve can function normally;&#x0D;&lt;br&gt;4. right-handed;&#x0D;&lt;br&gt;5. no abnormal mental, cognitive, and language function, and qualified for fMRI and stimulations;&#x0D;&lt;br&gt;6. willing to undergo regular follow-up and related evaluation;&#x0D;&lt;br&gt;7. the consent form has been detailly informed and signed.
    </Inclusion_Criteria>
    <Exclusion_Criteria>Exclusion criteria: 1. The general condition can't experience operation;&#x0D;&lt;br&gt;2. not qualified to accept the magnetic or electrical stimulation based on the existing medical condition;&#x0D;&lt;br&gt;3. not qualified to accept the electrophysiology or fMRI test based on the existing mental and physical condition;&#x0D;&lt;br&gt;4. impairment cognitive or language function.
    </Exclusion_Criteria>
    <Condition>facial nerve palsy
    </Condition>
    <Intervention>1:Repetitive transcranial magnetic stimulation;2:peripheral electrical nerve stimulation;3:Repetitive transcranial magnetic stimulation and peripheral electrical nerve stimulation;
    </Intervention>
    <Primary_outcome>facial movement evaluation;Electrophysiology;Functional magnetic resonance imaging;
    </Primary_outcome>
    <Source_Support>self-financing
    </Source_Support>
    <Ethics_review_status>Approved
    </Ethics_review_status>
    <Ethics_review_approval_date>14/09/2020
    </Ethics_review_approval_date>
    <Ethics_review_contact_name/>
    <Ethics_review_contact_address>Xiao Shuping
    </Ethics_review_contact_address>
    <Ethics_review_contact_phone/>
    <Ethics_review_contact_email/>
    <results_url_link/>
    
  </Trial>

    
  <Trial><Export_date>02/03/2024 14:32:58</Export_date>
    <Internal_Number>13384209
    </Internal_Number>
    <TrialID>ISRCTN89158865
    </TrialID>
    <Last_Refreshed_on>3 October 2023
    </Last_Refreshed_on>
    <Public_title>Investigating the use of taping for children with cerebral palsy
    </Public_title>
    <Scientific_title>Elastic therapeutic taping (ETT) of the thigh in children with Cerebral Palsy and spastic hemiplegia or diplegia: a phase 1 trial investigating mechanisms of action and a phase 2 proof of concept cross over trial investigating the effects of ETT on neuromuscular impairment and walking                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                   
    </Scientific_title>
    <Primary_sponsor>Plymouth University
    </Primary_sponsor>
    <Retrospective_flag>No
    </Retrospective_flag>
    <Date_registration3>20200218
    </Date_registration3>
    <Date_registration>18/02/2020
    </Date_registration>
    <Source_Register>ISRCTN
    </Source_Register>
    <web_address>https://www.isrctn.com/ISRCTN89158865
    </web_address>
    <Recruitment_Status>Not Recruiting
    </Recruitment_Status>
    <other_records>No
    </other_records>
    <Inclusion_agemin/>
    <Inclusion_agemax/>
    <Inclusion_gender>Both
    </Inclusion_gender>
    <Date_enrollement>02/01/2019
    </Date_enrollement>
    <Target_size>35
    </Target_size>
    <Study_type>Interventional
    </Study_type>
    <Study_design>Randomised; Both; Design type: Treatment, Device, Physical, Rehabilitation, Cross-sectional (Treatment)
    </Study_design>
    <Phase>Not Applicable
    </Phase>
    <Countries>United Kingdom;England
    </Countries>
    <Contact_Firstname/>
    <Contact_Lastname/>
    <Contact_Address/>
    <Contact_Email/>
    <Contact_Tel/>
    <Contact_Affiliation/>
    <Inclusion_Criteria>Inclusion criteria: 1. 6 to 16 years old&lt;br&gt;2. Diagnosis of cerebral palsy&lt;br&gt;3. Gross Motor Classification Scale (GMFCS I to III)&lt;br&gt;4. Able to stand up and walk without adult assistance&lt;br&gt;5. Increased muscle tone
    </Inclusion_Criteria>
    <Exclusion_Criteria>Exclusion criteria: 1. Surgery or Botulinum Toxin Injections in the last 3 months&lt;br&gt;2. Medical advice to limit weight bearing or leg movement&lt;br&gt;3. Popliteal angle &gt; 80o
    </Exclusion_Criteria>
    <Condition>Cerebral palsy &lt;br&gt;Nervous System Diseases &lt;br&gt;Cerebral palsy
    </Condition>
    <Intervention>Target Population: Ambulant children with spastic hemiplegic or diplegic cerebral palsy (Gross Motor Classification I-III) will be recruited through two routes: &lt;br&gt;1. Participants will be recruited via child development centres within South Devon and Somerset (n=4) and gait lab clinics based at the University of the West of England and Plymouth University. Children and families who fulfil the inclusion criteria will be approached by their treating therapist to explain the study and provide an information sheet. People who are interested in being contacted will fill out their preferred contact details on a contact form which will be sent to the PI. &lt;br&gt;2. Children will be recruited via CP Sport. Children and families will be contacted via a named gatekeeper at CP Sport. They will send out information sheets and contact forms. In addition, we will arrange a short presentation and put up posters about the study at CP Sport activity days. Families who are interested in the study will contact the research team.  In both cases, once contact has been made with the research team, the PI will then contact the family to discuss the study further. If people are willing, an appointment will be made and informed consent and assent obtained.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Phase 1: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study Site: This study takes place at the Peninsula Allied Health Centre in Plymouth. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study Design: It is a cross-sectional design where the child attends on one occasion and their response to taping or not taping the thigh on stretch reflex activation is assessed.&lt;br&gt;Participant characteristics:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The following data would be gathered:&lt;br&gt;(a) Demographics&lt;br&gt;(b) Gross motor function classification scale and classification of CP (diplegia vs hemiplegia)&lt;br&gt;(c) Tardieu test for the hamstrings which is reliable following training. This is a clinical tes
    </Intervention>
    <Primary_outcome>Measures taken within 1 session, T=0 baseline, T1= post intervention:&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Phase 1: &lt;br&gt;Stretch reflex size: surface electromyography will measure medial hamstrings and rectus femoris activity. Stretch reflex amplitude will be determined as the mean between the onset and offset of the muscle activation (defined as the point when the rectified EMG signal falls above/below a target indicated by the mean pre-stretch baseline period + 2 standard deviations for at least 10 ms)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Phase 2: &lt;br&gt;Hamstring extensibility, measured with a goniometer: the test leg will be moved to 90° hip flexion and then popliteal angle will be measured
    </Primary_outcome>
    <Secondary_outcome>Measures taken within 1 session, T=0 baseline, T1= post intervention:&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Phase 1:&lt;br&gt;1. Stretch reflex latency, measured using  the same EMG data as for the primary outcome, the analysis  for the stretch reflex onset will be determined by the time the EMG rises above/below a level (baseline mean + 2 standard deviations) for at least 10 ms&lt;br&gt;2. Passive stiffness, measured using the data from the customised motor, this measures the torque (by an in series torque transducer) and motor position. Passive stiffness will be determined as the change in torque/change in position over a 300 ms window immediately before and after the stretch, so the change in resistance from before and during the passive movement will show the passive stiffness&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Phase 2:&lt;br&gt;1. Clinical measure of stiffness (modified Wartenburg's test). The participant will be lying on their front with the lower leg over the edge of the bed. The leg will be raised and allowed to drop with gravity. The researchers will record how quickly the leg drops using sensors that are placed above and below the knee and attached using Velcro straps. They will record three drops and the test should take 3 minutes&lt;br&gt;2. Time to sit to stand: how quickly the child can stand up from sitting 5 times. The use of arms and any aids to help push up are allowed if needed. There will be a two-minute maximum time allowance.&lt;br&gt;3. Knee velocity while walking: the speed of knee movement as the child walks 5 m and the time they take to walk over the distance. The child should use any walking aids typically used. &lt;br&gt;4. Quality during walking, measured using the Quality FM during the 5-meter walkthrough video analysis
    </Secondary_outcome>
    <Secondary_ID>Nil known;Nil known;CPMS 39161
    </Secondary_ID>
    <Source_Support>Chartered Society of Physiotherapy Charitable Trust; Grant Codes: NP/17/01
    </Source_Support>
    <Ethics_review_status/>
    <Ethics_review_approval_date>01/01/1900
    </Ethics_review_approval_date>
    <Ethics_review_contact_name/>
    <Ethics_review_contact_address>Old ethics approval format; Approved 11/09/2018, South West - Cornwall &amp; Plymouth Research Ethics Committee (Level 3, Block B, Whitefriars, Lewins Mead, Bristol, BS1 2NT, UK; Tel: +44 (0)207 104 8017; Email: nrescommittee.southwest-cornwall-plymouth@nhs.net), REC ref: 18/SW/0180EC
    </Ethics_review_contact_address>
    <Ethics_review_contact_phone/>
    <Ethics_review_contact_email/>
    <results_date_completed>31/08/2022
    </results_date_completed>
    <results_url_link/>
    
  </Trial>

    
  <Trial><Export_date>02/03/2024 14:32:58</Export_date>
    <Internal_Number>13089080
    </Internal_Number>
    <TrialID>RBR-6bvnx6
    </TrialID>
    <Last_Refreshed_on>29 May 2023
    </Last_Refreshed_on>
    <Public_title>Physical therapy to improve walking in people with Parkinson's Disease.
    </Public_title>
    <Scientific_title>Effect of the transcranial direct current stimulation (tDCS) associated with Physical Therapy on freezing of gait and functionality after Parkinson’s disease.&#x0D;
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                
    </Scientific_title>
    <Primary_sponsor>Universidade Federal do Espírito Santo
    </Primary_sponsor>
    <Retrospective_flag>No
    </Retrospective_flag>
    <Date_registration3>20190923
    </Date_registration3>
    <Date_registration>23/09/2019
    </Date_registration>
    <Source_Register>REBEC
    </Source_Register>
    <web_address>http://ensaiosclinicos.gov.br/rg/RBR-6bvnx6
    </web_address>
    <Recruitment_Status>Recruiting
    </Recruitment_Status>
    <other_records>No
    </other_records>
    <Inclusion_agemin>40Y
    </Inclusion_agemin>
    <Inclusion_agemax>100Y
    </Inclusion_agemax>
    <Inclusion_gender>-
    </Inclusion_gender>
    <Date_enrollement>01/09/2019
    </Date_enrollement>
    <Target_size/>
    <Study_type>Intervention
    </Study_type>
    <Study_design>A two-arm paralell double-blind randomized controlled trial.
    </Study_design>
    <Phase>N/A
    </Phase>
    <Countries>Brazil
    </Countries>
    <Contact_Firstname>Fernando
    </Contact_Firstname>
    <Contact_Lastname>Âreas
    </Contact_Lastname>
    <Contact_Address>Av Marechal Campos 1468 Maruípe 29043900 - Vitória, ES - Brasil
    </Contact_Address>
    <Contact_Email>fernandozanela@hotmail.com
    </Contact_Email>
    <Contact_Tel>+55-027-996087012
    </Contact_Tel>
    <Contact_Affiliation>Universidade Federal do Espírito Santo
    </Contact_Affiliation>
    <Inclusion_Criteria>Inclusion criteria: Participants will be individuals with Parkinson’s Disease, who will be eligible, if they: are over 40 years of age; are able to walk at least 14 meters, independently, with or without assistive devices; walk at speeds lower than 1.1 m/s; have experienced freezing episodes over the past month, according to the Part I of the New Freezing of Gait Questionnaire (Nieuwboer et al 2009); have adapted to their current anti-Parkinsonian medication for at least 2 weeks; provide written consent.&#x0D;&lt;br&gt;
    </Inclusion_Criteria>
    <Exclusion_Criteria>Exclusion criteria: They will be excluded, if they: have cognitive deficits, which will be screened by the Mini-Mental State Examination. The cut-off scores are 26 for people with high levels of education, 18 for people with elementary and middle levels, and 13 for illiterate people (Bertolucci et al 1994);suffer from unstable cardiovascular disease or other uncontrolled chronic conditions that would interfere with the safety and conduct of the training and testing protocol or interpretation of the results; over 100 years of age.&#x0D;&lt;br&gt;
    </Exclusion_Criteria>
    <Condition>Parkinson Disease.;C10.228.140.079.862.500
    </Condition>
    <Intervention>24 individuals will be recruited. The intervention is physical therapy including task-specific walking training associated with transcranial direct current stimulation (tDCS), 30 min per day, three days per week, over four weeks. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A stimulator (DC-Stimulator Plus, NeuroConn, Ilmenau, Germany) will deliver a continuous direct current by a saline-soaked pair of surface sponge electrodes (size of electrodes 35cm2).  The anode will be placed at the Cz position on the scalp, corressponding to the location of the supplementary motor area, in accordance with the International EEG 10/20 system (Klem et al 1999, Yotnuengnit et al 2018). The cathode will be positioned over the supraorbital area. Participants will receive electrical stimulation of 2 mA, during the walking training. The 30-min sessions of task-specific walking training will include practicing part of the task (about 10 min), where the muscles are working in a manner similar to a full task performance and practicing the whole task (about 20 min).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The control group will undertake the task-specific walking training associated with a sham- tDCS. The control group will receive the same walking training, electrodes positioning and testing schedule as the experimental group. This will avoid bias related to type and amount of attention given to participants. If the addition of tDCS proves to be effective, the control group may receive the experimental training program after the experiment is complete.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The intervention will be undertaken in Clinics of Physiotherapy at the Universidade Federal do Espírito Santo. To encourage the participants to comply with the protocol, both groups will be asked to sign a symbolic contract of commitment to the proposed protocol. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;12 partcipants will be randomi;Other;E02.779;E02.331.800;E01.370.600.250
    </Intervention>
    <Primary_outcome>The primary outcome is comfortable walking speed, measured by the 10-m Walk Test, and reported in m/s.
    </Primary_outcome>
    <Secondary_outcome>Walking step length and cadence will be measured using the 10-m Walk Test. Step length will be calculated by dividing the covered distance, i.e., 10m, by the number of steps to cover the distance, and reported in meters.  Walking cadence will be calculated by dividing the number of steps by the time to cover the distance, i.e., 10m, and reported in steps/min.;Walking confidence will be measured using the Brazilian version of the modified Gait Efficacy Scale, and reported as scores ranging from 10 to 100. ;Mobility will be measured by the Timed-up and Go Test (TUG) and reported as seconds. ;Freezing of gait will be measured using Parts II and III of the New Freezing of Gait Questionnaire, and reported as scores ranging from 0 to 28, where higher scores indicate worse episodes of freezing.;Fear of falling will be measured using the Brazilian version of the Falls Efficacy Scale – International (FES-I Brazil), and reported as scores ranging from 16 to 64, where higher scores indicate greater fear of falling. ;The number of falls will be recorded by the use of a “falls diary” , and the proportion of fallers in each group will also be compared. 
    </Secondary_outcome>
    <Source_Support>Fundação de Amparo à Pesquisa e Inovação do Espírito Santo 
    </Source_Support>
    <Secondary_Sponsor>Universidade Federal do Espírito Santo
    </Secondary_Sponsor>
    <results_url_link/>
    
  </Trial>
</Trials_downloaded_from_ICTRP>